{"allRoundData":[{"name":"Preterit","timeLimitInSeconds":10,"pointsAddedForCorrectAnswer":10,"questions":[{"questionText":"What does abandoné mean in English?","answers":[{"answerText":"left behind","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"hugged","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encompassed","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"bored","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does the informal you of \"hugged\" in Spanish?","answers":[{"answerText":"abandonamos ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abrieron ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abrazaste ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abusaron ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct part of speech for abundó?","answers":[{"answerText":"were plentiful ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"was plentiful ","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What does aburrimos mean in English?","answers":[{"answerText":"boarded ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"bored ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abused ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encompassed ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct part of speech for abordaron?","answers":[{"answerText":"I boarded","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"he, she, you boarded","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"you all boarded","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"we boarded","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does abusamos mean in English?","answers":[{"answerText":"left behind ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encompassed ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"opened ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abused ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does finished mean in Spanish?","answers":[{"answerText":"abarcaron ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcaste ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"acabamos ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abarcaron ","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the informal you of \"encompassed\" in Spanish?","answers":[{"answerText":"abandonaron ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcó  ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"abrazaron ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abarcaste ","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is aburriste in English?","answers":[{"answerText":"hugged ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"bored ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"left behind","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"was plentiful","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct part of speech for abusaron?","answers":[{"answerText":"You All","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"They","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"You","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is absorbed in Spanish?","answers":[{"answerText":"abarcamos ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"acabó ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abandonaron ","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"absorbieron ","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the meaning of abrieron?","answers":[{"answerText":"opened ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"hugged","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"left behind","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"encompassed","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct part of speech of abandoné?","answers":[{"answerText":"We","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"I","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"You","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"They","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does abusamos mean in English?","answers":[{"answerText":"hugged","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"bored","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"left behind","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"abused ","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What is the correct part of speech of abundamos?","answers":[{"answerText":"You","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"They","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"We","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"You All","isCorrect":true}]}]}]}